Finding aid for the Hearst Corporation Los Angeles Examiner photographs, negatives and clippings - oversize portrait and subject files 7000.3
USC Libraries Special Collections
- Oversize Subject Files
  - B
    - Baseball -- Los Angeles Dodgers -- 1958 -- Playing at the Coliseum (Box 254, Folder 3)
    - Baseball -- Los Angeles Dodgers -- 1959 (Box 254, Folder 5)
    - Baseball -- Los Angeles Dodgers -- 1960 (Box 254, Folder 4)
    - Baseball -- Los Angeles Dodgers -- 1960 (Box 254, Folder 6)
    - Baseball -- Los Angeles Dodgers Versus Milwaukee Braves (Box 255, Folder 14)
    - Baseball -- Major leagues -- Miscellaneous (Box 252, Folder 4-5)
    - Baseball -- Miscellaneous (Box 249, Folder 1-4)
    - Baseball -- New York Giants (Box 253, Folder 1)
    - Baseball -- New York Yankees (Box 253, Folder 2)
    - Baseball -- San Francisco Giants -- 1958 (Box 253, Folder 3)
    - Baseball -- San Francisco Seals (Box 253, Folder 4)
    - Baseball -- Stadiums (Box 252, Folder 6)
    - Baseball -- Team -- Group Shots (Box 252, Folder 7)
    - Baseball -- World Series -- 1945 (Box 248, Folder 1)
    - Baseball -- World Series -- 1946 (Box 248, Folder 2)
    - Baseball -- World Series -- 1947 (Box 248, Folder 3)
    - Baseball -- World Series -- 1948-1949 (Box 248, Folder 4)
    - Baseball -- World Series -- 1950 (Box 248, Folder 5)
    - Baseball -- World Series -- 1951 (Box 248, Folder 6)
    - Baseball -- World Series -- 1952 (Box 247, Folder 1-2)
    - Baseball -- World Series -- 1953 (Box 247, Folder 3)
    - Baseball -- World Series -- 1954 (Box 247, Folder 4-5)
    - Baseball -- World Series -- 1955 (Box 247, Folder 6)
    - Baseball -- World Series -- 1956 (Box 256, Folder 1)
    - Baseball -- World Series -- 1957 (Box 256, Folder 2-3)
    - Baseball -- World Series -- 1958 (Box 256, Folder 4)
    - Baseball -- World Series -- 1959 (Box 256, Folder 5)
    - Baseball -- World Series -- 1960 (Box 256, Folder 6)
    - Baseball -- World Series -- 1961 -- New York Yankees Versus Cincinnati Reds (Box 256, Folder 7)
    - Basketball -- College and University Teams (Box 257, Folder 8)
    - Basketball -- High School Teams (Box 258, Folder 1)
    - Basketball -- Loyola University (Box 257, Folder 9)
    - Basketball -- Miscellaneous (Box 257, Folder 1-7)
    - Basketball -- Professional -- Los Angeles Lakers (Box 258, Folder 2)
    - Basketball -- UCLA (Box 257, Folder 10-18)
    - Basketball -- USC (Box 258, Folder 3 - 9)
    - Beach Scenes (Box 245, Folder 1)
    - Beauties (Box 245, Folder 2)
    - Belgium (Box 245, Folder 3)
    - Bill of Rights Day (Box 245, Folder 4)
    - Birds (Box 245, Folder 5)
    - Blind (Box 245, Folder 6)
    - Blood -- Bank and Donors (Box 245, Folder 7)
    - Boats -- Fishing, Sail, Speed, etc. (Box 245, Folder 8)
    - Bolivia (Box 246, Folder 1)
    - Bombs (Box 246, Folder 2)
    - Bonds (Box 246, Folder 3)
    - Borneo (Box 246, Folder 4)
    - Boxing (Box 246, Folder 5)
    - Boy Scouts (Box 246, Folder 7)
    - Boy Scouts -- Jamboree -- Special Section -- July 19, 1953 (Box 246, Folder 8-10)
    - Boys -- Miscellaneous -- Camps and Clubs (Box 246, Folder 6)
    - Brazil (Box 249, Folder 5)
    - Bridges (Box 249, Folder 6)
    - Buildings -- Miscellaneous (Box 249, Folder 7)
    - Bulgaria (Box 249, Folder 8)
    - Bullfighting (Box 249, Folder 9)
    - Burma -- And Burma Road (Box 249, Folder 10)
  - C
    - California -- Bakersfield -- Reconstruction Only (Box 259, Folder 2)
    - California -- Balboa, Newport (Box 259, Folder 3)
    - California -- Bel-Air (Box 259, Folder 4)
    - California -- Beverly Hills (Box 259, Folder 5)
    - California -- C-D Miscellaneous (Box 259, Folder 6)
    - California -- Cities and Places -- A-B Miscellaneous (Box 259, Folder 1)
    - California -- Compton (Box 259, Folder 7)
    - California -- E Miscellaneous (Box 259, Folder 8)
    - California -- F-K Miscellaneous (Box 259, Folder 9)
    - California -- Hollywood - General (Box 259, Folder 10)
    - California -- Hollywood -- Hollywood Bowl -- Audience (Box 259, Folder 11)
    - California -- Hollywood -- Hollywood Bowl -- "Faust" Performance (With Negatives) (Box 259, Folder 12)
    - California -- Hollywood -- Hollywood Bowl -- Miscellaneous Views (Includes Entrance, Sculpture, Promotion, Map), With Negatives (Box 259, Folder 13)
    - California -- Hollywood -- Hollywood Bowl -- Panoramas (Box 259, Folder 14)
    - California -- Hollywood -- Hollywood Bowl -- Panoramas (With Negatives) (Box 259, Folder 15)
    - California -- Hollywood -- Hollywood Bowl -- Panoramas -- Night Views (Box 259, Folder 16)
    - California -- Laguna, Lake Crowley (Box 259, Folder 17)
    - California -- Lakewood (Box 259, Folder 18)
    - California -- Lancaster (Box 259, Folder 19)
    - California -- Pasadena -- Tournament of Roses -- 1958-1959 (Box 260, Folder 1)
    - California -- Pomona (Box 260, Folder 2)
    - California -- Redondo Beach (Box 260, Folder 3)
    - California -- S-T (Box 260, Folder 4)
    - California -- San-Santa -- Miscellaneous (Box 260, Folder 5)
    - California -- San Diego (Box 260, Folder 6)
    - California -- Santa Barbara (Box 260, Folder 7)
    - California -- San Simeon -- Hearst Ranch (Box 260, Folder 8)
    - California -- U-Z (Box 260, Folder 9)
    - Canals -- Miscellaneous (Box 260, Folder 10)
    - Canada -- Civil, Army, Navy (Box 260, Folder 11)
    - Ca-Cm (Box 261, Folder 1)
    - California -- Long Beach (Box 262, Folder 1-3)
    - California -- Long Beach -- Subsidence -- Land Sinking (Box 262, Folder 4)
    - California -- Miscellaneous (Box 261, Folder 2)
    - California -- M-N -- Miscellaneous (Box 262, Folder 5)
    - California -- O-R -- Miscellaneous (Box 262, Folder 6)
    - California -- Pasadena (Box 262, Folder 7)
    - California -- Pasadena -- Tournament of Roses -- 1947 and Before (Box 263, Folder 2)
    - California -- Pasadena -- Tournament of Roses -- 1948 (Box 263, Folder 1)
    - California -- Pasadena -- Tournament of Roses Parade -- January 1, 1949 (Box 263, Folder 3)
    - California -- Pasadena -- Tournament of Roses -- January 1, 1950 (Box 263, Folder 4)
    - California -- Pasadena -- Tournament of Roses -- 1951, 1952 (Box 263, Folder 9)
    - California -- Pasadena -- Tournament of Roses -- 1953 (Box 263, Folder 8)
    - California -- Pasadena -- Tournament of Roses -- January 1, 1954 (Box 263, Folder 5)
    - California -- Pasadena -- Tournament of Roses -- Parades -- 1955 (Box 262, Folder 9)
    - California -- Pasadena -- Rose Tournament -- 1955, 1956 (Box 263, Folder 6)
    - California -- Pasadena -- Rose Tournament -- 1957 (Box 263, Folder 7)
    - California -- Pasadena -- Tournament of Roses -- 1962 (Box 262, Folder 8)
    - Cartoons -- Miscellaneous (Box 264, Folder 1)
    - Cartoons -- Hubenthal (Box 264, Folder 2)
    - Cats (Box 264, Folder 3)
    - Cattle (Box 264, Folder 4)
    - Cemeteries (Box 264, Folder 5)
    - Charts (Box 264, Folder 6)
    - Children (Box 265, Folder 1-5)
    - Chimpanzees (Box 265, Folder 6)
    - China (Box 265, Folder 7)
    - China -- Nationalist Army (Box 265, Folder 8)
    - Choirs -- Miscellaneous (Box 265, Folder 9)
    - Churches -- Catholic -- Los Angeles -- Miscellaneous (Box 266, Folder 1)
    - Churches -- Catholic -- Los Angeles -- St. Vibiana's Cathedral (Box 266, Folder 2)
    - Churches -- Christian Science (Box 266, Folder 3)
    - Churches -- Congregational (Box 266, Folder 4)
    - Churches -- Episcopalian (Box 266, Folder 5)
    - Churches -- Greek Orthodox (Box 266, Folder 6)
    - Churches -- Jewish (Box 266, Folder 7)
    - Churches -- Lutheran (Box 266, Folder 8)
    - Churches -- Methodist (Box 266, Folder 9)
    - Churches -- Mormon (Box 266, Folder 10)
    - Churches -- Presbyterian (Box 266, Folder 11)
    - Churches -- Russian Orthodox (Box 266, Folder 12)
    - Churches -- Seventh Day Adventist (Box 266, Folder 13)
    - Churches -- Wilshire Christian Church (Box 266, Folder 14)
    - Christmas (Box 267, Folder 1-10)
    - Churches -- Baptist (Box 267, Folder 12)
    - Churches -- Catholic -- Miscellaneous (Box 267, Folder 13)
    - Churches -- Miscellaneous (Box 267, Folder 11)
    - Circus (Box 271, Folder 1)
    - Civilian defense (Box 271, Folder 2)
    - Ciu-Cz (Box 271, Folder 3)
    - Coal -- And Coal Miners (Box 271, Folder 4)
    - Colombia (Box 271, Folder 5)
    - Communism -- Miscellaneous (Box 271, Folder 6)
    - Community Chest (Box 272, Folder 1)
    - Conference (Box 272, Folder 2)
    - Conferences -- Big four -- Geneva, Switzerland -- July, 1955 (Box 272, Folder 3)
    - Congress -- Miscellaneous (Box 272, Folder 4)
    - Conscription -- WWII Draft Lottery (Box 272, Folder 5)
    - Constitution -- Copy of (Box 272, Folder 6)
    - Contests -- Beauty -- Miscellaneous (Box 272, Folder 7 - 10)
    - Contests -- Beauty -- Miscellaneous, Including Miss Universe (Box 272, Folder 11 - 16)
    - Contests -- Beauty -- Miss America -- 1955 (Box 272, Folder 17 - 18)
    - Contests -- Miscellaneous (Box 272, Folder 19 - 23)
    - Conventions and Conferences (Box 268, Folder 1)
    - Cotton (Box 268, Folder 2)
    - Crews -- Rowing (Box 268, Folder 5)
    - Crime -- Hijacking (Box 273, Folder 1)
    - Crime -- Miscellaneous (Box 268, Folder 3)
    - Crime -- Murder (Box 268, Folder 4)
    - Crime -- Prison Breaks (Box 273, Folder 2)
    - Crime -- Robbery (Box 273, Folder 3)
    - Crime -- Shootings (Box 273, Folder 4)
    - Crime -- Theft -- Miscellaneous (Box 273, Folder 5)
    - Crime -- Trials -- Duncan Case -- Trial Shots (Box 273, Folder 6)
    - Crowds (Box 273, Folder 7)
    - Cuba -- Miscellaneous (Box 273, Folder 8)
    - Cults -- Religious Sects (Box 273, Folder 9)
    - Cults -- Polygamist (Box 273, Folder 10)
    - Cyclotron (Box 273, Folder 11)
    - Czechoslovakia (Box 273, Folder 12)
  - D
    - Daa-Deb (Box 269, Folder 1)
    - Dairies (Box 269, Folder 2-3)
    - Dams (Box 269, Folder 4)
    - Dams -- Whittier Narrows (Box 269, Folder 5)
    - Dancing (Box 269, Folder 6-7)
    - Deaf -- Miscellaneous (Box 269, Folder 8)
    - Deer (Box 269, Folder 9)
    - Dem-Dez (Box 269, Folder 10)
    - Dia-Diu (Box 269, Folder 11)
    - Diseases (Box 269, Folder 12)
    - Disneyland (Box 270, Folder 1)
    - Displaced Persons (Box 270, Folder 2-3)
    - Div (Box 270, Folder 4)
    - Doa-Dol (Box 270, Folder 5)
    - Doctors (Box 270, Folder 6)
    - Doctors -- Training -- Special Feature by Chris Clausen on Doctor Robert Vannix (Box 270, Folder 7)
    - Dogs -- Miscellaneous (Box 270, Folder 8-11)
    - Dogs -- Miscellaneous (Box 274, Folder 1)
    - Dom-Doz (Box 270, Folder 12)
    - Dra-Dz (Box 274, Folder 2)
    - Dutch East Indies (Box 274, Folder 3)
  - E
    - E-Ez (Box 274, Folder 4)
    - Earth (Box 274, Folder 5)
    - Earthquakes (Box 274, Folder 6)
    - Earthquakes -- Mexico City -- July 28, 1957 (Box 276, Folder 1)
    - Earthquakes -- Pacific Northwest -- 1949 (Box 276, Folder 2)
    - Earthquakes -- Southern California -- Bakersfield -- August 22, 1952 (Box 276, Folder 3)
    - Earthquakes -- Southern California -- Tehachapi -- July 21, 1952 (Box 276, Folder 4)
    - Easter -- Miscellaneous -- Not Religious Services (Box 276, Folder 5-7)
    - Education -- Mental and Physical (Box 276, Folder 8)
    - Egypt (Box 276, Folder 9)
    - Electronics (Box 276, Folder 10)
    - Elephants (Box 276, Folder 11)
    - England (Box 275, Folder 1)
    - England -- Army and Royal Armed Forces (Box 275, Folder 2)
    - England -- London (Box 275, Folder 3-5)
    - England -- Navy (Box 275, Folder 6)
    - Eskimos (Box 277A, Folder 1)
    - Ethiopia -- Army, Civil, and Navy (Box 277A, Folder 2)
    - Examiner -- Boxing (Box 277A, Folder 3)
    - Examiner -- Christmas Benefit (Box 277A, Folder 4)
    - Examiner -- Contest (Box 277A, Folder 5-9)
    - Examiner -- Miscellaneous (Box 277, Folder 1-5)
    - Expeditions (Box 277A, Folder 10)
    - Explosions (Box 277A, Folder 11)
    - Expositions (Box 277A, Folder 12-13)
    - Expositions -- Los Angeles County Fair (Box 277A, Folder 14)
    - Examiner -- Hall of Fame -- Drawings (Box 288, Folder 1)
    - Examiner -- Motor log (Box 288, Folder 2-5)
    - Examiner -- Photo awards (Box 288, Folder 6)
    - Examiner -- Scholastic Sports Association and Carriers (Box 288, Folder 7)
    - Examiner -- Series (Box 288, Folder 8)
    - Examiner -- Swimming (Box 288, Folder 9)
    - Examiner -- War Wounded Fund (Box 288, Folder 10)
    - Examiner -- Youth Forum (Box 290, Folder 1)
  - F
    - Fa-Fu (Box 290, Folder 2-6)
    - Fairs (Box 290, Folder 7- 11)
    - Farmers (Box 290, Folder 12)
    - Fashion (Box 291, Folder 1-8)
    - Fashions (Box 289, Folder 1-10)
    - Fencing (Box 292, Folder 1)
    - Fiestas -- Miscellaneous (Box 292, Folder 2)
    - Fiestas -- Santa Barbara (Box 292, Folder 3)
    - Finland (Box 292, Folder 4)
    - Fires -- States A to J (Box 296, Folder 2)
    - Fires -- States K to Q (Box 295, Folder 1-8)
    - Fires -- States R to Z (Box 295, Folder 13)
    - Fires -- Brush -- California -- Laurel Canyon Lookout Mountain -- July 10, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - Fires -- Brush -- California -- 1960 (Box 297, Folder 1)
    - Fires -- Brush -- Local -- Malibu -- 1958 (Box 279, Folder 6)
    - Fires -- Brush -- Local -- 1955 (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - Fires -- Brush -- Local -- 1958 (Box 282, Folder 4)
    - Fires -- Brush -- Local -- 1959 (Box 282, Folder 5)
    - Fires -- Brush -- 1948-1949 (Box 294, Folder 2-6)
    - Fires -- Brush -- 1953-1954 (Box 294, Folder 8)
    - Fires -- Brush -- Santa Barbara -- 1955 (Box 280, Folder 3)
    - Fires -- Brush -- Topanga -- Malibu -- Beverly Hills -- December 31, 1958 (Box 280, Folder 4)
    - Fires -- California -- Malibu -- 1956 (Box 279, Folder 2)
    - Fires -- California -- Malibu -- 1957 (Box 279, Folder 3-5)
    - Fires -- Chicago, Illinois (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - Fires -- Firemen (Box 283)
    - Fires -- Forest -- 1948-1949 (Box 278, Folder 6)
    - Fires -- Forest -- 1950-1952 (Box 278, Folder 5)
    - Fires -- Forest -- 1953 (Box 278, Folder 4)
    - Fires -- Forest -- 1954 (Box 278, Folder 3)
    - Fires -- Forest -- 1960 (Box 278, Folder 2)
    - Fires -- Local -- 1948 to 1949 (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - Fires -- Local and State -- 1950 (Box 281, Folder 2)
    - Fires -- Local and State -- 1952 (Box 281, Folder 4)
    - Fires -- Local and State -- 1953 (Box 282, Folder 1-2)
    - Fires -- Local and State -- 1954 (Box 282, Folder 3)
    - Fires -- Miscellaneous (Box 294, Folder 1)
    - Fires -- New York (Box 295, Folder 9-12)
    - Fires -- Oil -- Hancock Oil Refinery -- Signal Hill (Box 280, Folder 5)
    - Fires -- Oil -- Through 1954 (Box 278, Folder 7)
    - Fires -- Ship (Box 296, Folder 1)
    - Fires -- State and local -- 1956 (Box 297, Folder 2)
    - Fires -- State and local -- 1957 (Box 297, Folder 3)
    - Fires -- Warner Brothers (Box 280, Folder 6)
    - Firms (Box 292, Folder 5-7)
    - Fishing -- Examiner Fishing Derby (Box 293, Folder 8)
    - Fishing -- Miscellaneous (Box 293, Folder 1-7)
    - Fishing -- Trout -- San Gabriel Valley (Box 293, Folder 9)
    - Flags and Flag Day (Box 293, Folder 10)
    - Flags - U.S. (Box 283, Folder 1)
    - Floods (Box 280, Folder 7)
    - Floods -- California (Box 287, Folder 1)
    - Floods -- Colorado (Box 287, Folder 2)
    - Floods -- Oregon (Box 287, Folder 3)
    - Floods -- Pennsylvania (Box 287, Folder 4-9)
    - Floods -- Texas (Box 287, Folder 10)
    - Floods -- United States -- 1960 (Box 287, Folder 11)
    - Florida -- Miscellaneous (Box 283, Folder 2)
    - Flowers (Box 283, Folder 4)
    - Flying Discs (Box 283, Folder 3)
    - Football -- Bowl games (Box 286, Folder 2-5)
    - Football -- Los Angeles Chargers (Box 284, Folder 2)
    - Football -- Los Angeles Rams (Box 284, Folder 3)
    - Football -- Miscellaneous (Box 284, Folder 1)
    - Football -- Miscellaneous (Box 286, Folder 1)
    - Football -- Professional Teams -- Miscellaneous -- 1958 (Box 286, Folder 6-8)
    - Football -- Rose Bowl game -- 1957-1960 (Box 286, Folder 9-12)
    - Football -- Stanford University (Box 285, Folder 12)
    - Football -- Universities -- A-M (Box 284, Folder 4)
    - Football -- Universities -- N-Z (Box 285, Folder 3-9)
    - Football -- University of California at Berkeley (Box 285, Folder 1)
    - Football -- University of Loyola at Los Angeles (Box 285, Folder 2)
    - Football -- University of Notre Dame (Box 285, Folder 10-11)
    - Forests -- Angeles National (Box 283, Folder 6)
    - Forests -- Trees (Box 283, Folder 5)
    - Formosa (Box 283, Folder 7)
    - Fourth of July (Box 283, Folder 8)
    - France (Box 300, Folder 1)
    - France -- Army (Box 300, Folder 2)
    - France -- Bombing Scenes (Box 300, Folder 3)
    - France -- German Occupation -- World War II (Box 300, Folder 4)
    - France -- Navy (Box 300, Folder 5)
  - G
    - Gas (Box 298, Folder 1)
    - Germany (Box 298, Folder 2-3)
    - Germany -- Army (Box 298, Folder 4)
    - Germany -- Berlin (Box 298, Folder 5)
    - Germany -- Berlin -- Blockade 1961 (Box 298, Folder 6)
    - Germany -- Bombing Scenes (Box 299, Folder 1)
    - Germany -- Defense (Box 299, Folder 2)
    - Germany -- Navy (Box 299, Folder 3)
    - Germany -- Surrender -- World War II (Box 299, Folder 4)
    - Gi-Gl (Box 299, Folder 5)
    - Girl Scouts (Box 299, Folder 6)
    - Goa-Goz (Box 299, Folder 7)
    - Gold (Box 299, Folder 8)
    - Golf (Box 299, Folder 9-11)
    - Golf -- Los Angeles Open (Box 299, Folder 12)
    - Ga-Gh (Box 300, Folder 6)
    - Gambling (Box 300, Folder 7-8)
    - Gambling -- Raids (Box 300, Folder 9)
    - Gambling -- Ships (Box 300, Folder 10)
    - Gorillas (Box 301, Folder 1-2)
    - Gra-Grz (Box 301, Folder 3)
    - Greece (Box 301, Folder 4)
    - Gua-Gui (Box 301, Folder 5)
    - Guj-Guz (Box 301, Folder 6)
    - Gy-Gz (Box 301, Folder 7)
  - H
    - H-Hz (Box 301, Folder 8)
    - Harbors -- Miscellaneous (Box 302, Folder 1)
    - Harbors -- Pearl (Box 302, Folder 2)
    - Highways -- Freeways -- Golden State (Box 302, Folder 6-7)
    - Highways -- Freeways -- Harbor (Box 302, Folder 8)
    - Highways -- Freeways -- Hollywood (Box 302, Folder 9)
    - Highways -- Freeways -- Interchanges (Box 302, Folder 4-5)
    - Highways -- Freeways -- Long Beach, Pasadena (Box 302, Folder 10)
    - Highways -- Freeways -- Maps (Box 302, Folder 11-13)
    - Highways -- Freeways -- Miscellaneous (Box 302, Folder 3)
    - Highways -- Freeways -- San Diego (Box 302, Folder 14)
    - Highways -- Freeways -- Santa Ana, Santa Monica (Box 302, Folder 15)
    - Historical pictures (Box 303, Folder 1)
    - Hockey -- Ice and Regular (Box 303, Folder 2)
    - Holland (Box 303, Folder 3)
    - Homes -- And Housing (Box 309, Folder 2-4)
    - Homes -- Interior (Box 309, Folder 5)
    - Homes -- Miscellaneous (Box 309, Folder 1)
    - Horses -- Race -- Miscellaneous (Box 303, Folder 5)
    - Horses -- Race By Name -- A-B (Box 306, Folder 1)
    - Horses -- Race By Name -- C (Box 305, Folder 1)
    - Horses -- Race By Name -- D-F (Box 305, Folder 2)
    - Horses -- Race By Name -- G-I (Box 305, Folder 3)
    - Horses -- Race By Name -- J-M (Box 305, Folder 4)
    - Horses -- Race By Name -- N-R (Box 305, Folder 5)
    - Horses -- Race By Name -- S-Z (Box 308, Folder 1)
    - Horses -- Races -- Swaps (Box 308, Folder 2)
    - Horses -- Racetracks -- Belmont (Box 307, Folder 1-2)
    - Horses -- Racetracks -- Churchill Downs (Box 304, Folder 6-11)
    - Horses -- Racetracks -- Del Mar (Box 307, Folder 3)
    - Horses -- Racetracks -- Hollywood Park -- 1958 (Box 307, Folder 5)
    - Horses -- Racetracks -- Hollywood Park -- 1959-1961 (Box 307, Folder 6)
    - Horses -- Racetracks -- Jamaica, New York (Box 307, Folder 4)
    - Horses -- Racetracks -- Los Alamitos (Box 307, Folder 7)
    - Horses -- Racetracks -- Miscellaneous (Box 304, Folder 1-5)
    - Horses -- Racetracks -- Pimlico (Box 306, Folder 2)
    - Horses -- Racetracks -- Pomona fair (Box 306, Folder 3)
    - Horses -- Racetracks -- Santa Anita -- Finish of Races (Box 306, Folder 4)
    - Horses -- Racetracks -- Santa Anita -- Harness Races (Box 306, Folder 5)
    - Horses -- Racetracks -- Santa Anita -- Horses Running at Track (Box 306, Folder 6)
    - Horses -- Racetracks -- Santa Anita -- Start of Races (Box 306, Folder 7)
    - Horses -- Racetracks -- Santa Anita -- Views of Track and Crowds (Box 306, Folder 8)
    - Horses -- Shows (Box 308, Folder 3)
    - Horses -- Steeplechases (Box 308, Folder 4)
    - Horses -- Sulk and Harness Racing (Box 303, Folder 6)
    - Horses -- Sulkey Races (Box 304, Folder 12)
    - Horses -- Tracks -- Agua Caliente -- 1955 to 1957 (Box 303, Folder 7)
    - Hospitals (Box 308, Folder 5-7)
    - Hospitals -- Birmingham (Box 308, Folder 8)
    - Hospitals -- Camarillo State (Box 309, Folder 6)
    - Hospitals -- Los Angeles County General (Box 309, Folder 7)
    - Hotels -- Miscellaneous (Box 309, Folder 8)
    - Housing (Box 309, Folder 9-12)
    - Housing -- Park La Brea (Box 309, Folder 13)
    - Hungary (Box 310, Folder 1)
  - I, J, K
    - I-Iz (Box 310, Folder 2)
    - I (Box 310, Folder 3-5)
    - Ice Capades (Box 310, Folder 6)
    - Ice Hockey (Box 310, Folder 7)
    - India (Box 310, Folder 8)
    - Indians (Box 311, Folder 1)
    - Italy -- Abbey of St. Benedict -- Destroyed by Allied Bombing (Box 311, Folder 3)
    - Italy -- Army (Box 311, Folder 2)
    - Italy -- Bombing Scenes (Box 311, Folder 4)
    - Indonesia, Republic of (Box 311, Folder 5)
    - Iran (Box 311, Folder 6)
    - Israel (Box 311, Folder 7)
    - Israel -- Inside Israel, 1956 -- Special Feature (Box 311, Folder 8)
    - Italy (Box 311, Folder 9)
    - Italy -- Navy (Box 311, Folder 10)
    - Italy -- Rome (Box 311, Folder 11)
    - Iwo Jima -- Flag Raising Statue (Box 312, Folder 1)
    - Ja-Jz (Box 312, Folder 2)
    - Japan -- Army (Box 312, Folder 3)
    - Japan -- Bombing Scenes (Box 312, Folder 4)
    - Japan -- Navy (Box 312, Folder 5-7)
    - Java (Box 312, Folder 8)
    - Jews (Box 312, Folder 9)
    - Juries -- Doctor R. Bernard Finch -- And Carol Tregoff -- Murder Trial (Box 312, Folder 11)
    - Juries -- Miscellaneous (Box 312, Folder 10)
    - Ka-Ku (Box 313, Folder 1)
    - Korea (Box 313, Folder 2-5)
    - Korea -- U.S. Army Atrocities (Box 314, Folder 1)
    - Korea -- U.S. Army -- Air Force (Box 313, Folder 6-11)
    - Korea -- U.S. Army -- Air Force -- Aerial Bombing Views (Box 313, Folder 12)
    - Korea -- War -- U.S. Marines -- Casualties (Box 313, Folder 13)
  - L
    - L -- Miscellaneous (Box 314, Folder 2)
    - Labor -- Farms (Box 314, Folder 4)
    - Labor -- Miscellaneous (Box 314, Folder 3)
    - Lakes -- Miscellaneous (Box 314, Folder 6)
    - Leopards (Box 314, Folder 7)
    - Las Vegas -- Helldorado days (Box 314, Folder 5)
    - Letters (Box 314, Folder 8)
    - Liberty Bell (Box 314, Folder 9)
    - Lions (Box 314, Folder 10)
    - Liquor (Box 314, Folder 11)
    - Litter -- Miscellaneous (Box 314, Folder 12)
    - Livestock Shows (Box 314, Folder 13)
    - Los Angeles -- Air views (Box 315, Folder 5/8/2012)
    - Los Angeles -- Buildings -- A-Z (Box 317, Folder 1-2)
    - Los Angeles -- Buildings -- City Hall (Box 317, Folder 3)
    - Los Angeles -- Buildings -- Civic Center (Box 315, Folder 11)
    - Los Angeles -- Bunker Hill Area (Box 315, Folder 9 - 10)
    - Los Angeles -- Civil defense (Box 316, Folder 1)
    - Los Angeles -- County -- Courthouse (Box 317, Folder 6)
    - Los Angeles -- County -- Miscellaneous (Box 317, Folder 4-5)
    - Los Angeles -- County -- Sheriffs Department (Box 317, Folder 7)
    - Los Angeles -- Fire Department (Box 316, Folder 3)
    - Los Angeles -- Harbor (Box 316, Folder 4)
    - Los Angeles -- Miscellaneous (Box 315, Folder 1-4)
    - Los Angeles -- Parks (Box 316, Folder 5)
    - Los Angeles -- Police Department (Box 316, Folder 6)
    - Los Angeles -- Sewage and Hyperion Project (Box 316, Folder 2)